Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection, 1999-2016.
AFC 2007/009
Quilt Alliance
17,495 items
33 containers (13 3/4 linear feet)
approximately 855 sound cassettes: analog.
approximately 310 sound files: digital, WAV.
1 videocassette (VHS): sound, color; 1/2 in.
approximately 425 photographic prints: color; various sizes.
more than 1840 images: digital, color, jpeg, tiff.
approximately 1200 folders (12,390 items)
approximately 665 digital documents (doc, .docx, .pdf, .rtf)
approximately 950 optical discs: digital; 4 3/4 in.
10 floppy disks; 3 1/2 in.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
This collection consists of sound recordings, transcripts and photographic images documenting interviews conducted as a part of Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories (QSOS) project. QSOS is one of several projects and partnerships created by the Quilt Alliance in an effort to preserve, document, and share the lives and stories of quilters and quiltmaking. The project began in 1999 and continued though 2016.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Herman, Bernard L., 1951-; Musgrave, Karen S., 1955-; Obama, Barack.; Pritchard, Gayle A., 1957-
Organizations
Alzheimer's Art Quilt Initiative.; American Indian Center of Chicago.; American Quilt Study Group.; Arizona Quilters Hall of Fame.; Asheville Quilt Guild.; Cal-Co Quilters' Guild.; Daughters of the American Revolution.; Hilos de la vida.; International Quilt Festival/Houston, sponsor.; Kentucky Quilt Project.; Naples Quilters Guild.; National Museum of Mexican Art.; National Quilting Association (U.S.); Ohio Reformatory for Women.; Quilt Alliance; Quilts, Inc.; Trinity Valley Quilters' Guild.; University of Delaware. Center for Material Culture Studies; Virginia Quilt Museum.; Walter Reed Army Medical Center.; Women of Colour Quilters Network.
Subjects
African American quiltmakers--Interviews.; Arpilleras.; Art quilts.; Folk art quilts.; Hand quilting.; Hispanic Americans--Interviews.; Machine quilting.; Male quiltmakers--Interviews.; Narrative art.; Needlework, Hmong.; Patriotic quilts.; Quilted goods.; Quilting--Exhibitions.; Quilting--Patterns.; Quilting--United States.; Quiltmakers--Societies, etc.; Quiltmakers--United States--Interviews.; Quilts--Alabama.; Quilts--Alaska.; Quilts--Anecdotes.; Quilts--Arizona.; Quilts--Arkansas.; Quilts--California.; Quilts--Canada.; Quilts--Colorado.; Quilts--Connecticut.; Quilts--Delaware.; Quilts--Denmark.; Quilts--Florida.; Quilts--France.; Quilts--Georgia (Republic); Quilts--Georgia.; Quilts--Germany.; Quilts--Hawaii.; Quilts--Idaho.; Quilts--Illinois.; Quilts--Indiana.; Quilts--Iowa.; Quilts--Kansas.; Quilts--Kentucky.; Quilts--Kenya.; Quilts--Louisiana.; Quilts--Maine.; Quilts--Maryland.; Quilts--Massachusetts.; Quilts--Michigan.; Quilts--Minnesota.; Quilts--Mississippi.; Quilts--Missouri.; Quilts--Montana.; Quilts--Nebraska.; Quilts--Nevada.; Quilts--New Hampshire.; Quilts--New Jersey.; Quilts--New Mexico.; Quilts--New York (State); Quilts--New Zealand.; Quilts--North Carolina.; Quilts--North Dakota.; Quilts--Ohio.; Quilts--Oklahoma.; Quilts--Oregon.; Quilts--Pennsylvania.; Quilts--Peru.; Quilts--Photographs.; Quilts--Rhode Island.; Quilts--South Carolina.; Quilts--South Dakota.; Quilts--Tennessee.; Quilts--Texas.; Quilts--United States Virgin Islands; Quilts--United States--Themes, motives.; Quilts--Utah.; Quilts--Vermont.; Quilts--Virginia.; Quilts--Washington (D.C.); Quilts--Washington (State); Quilts--West Virginia.; Quilts--Wisconsin.; Quilts--Wyoming.; Scrap quilts.; Storytelling.; Women artists--Interviews.
Places
United States--Social life and customs.
Titles
Alliance for American Quilts interview collection 1999-2016; Project title: Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories
Form/Genre
Interviews (Sound recordings).; Interviews.; Manuscripts.; Oral histories.; Photographs.; Video recordings.
Arrangement
The materials are conceptually arranged in two series: 1. Administrative files and 2. Interviews. The Interviews series is arranged in record groups for each Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories (QSOS) project, and further subdivided into subseries for each interview. Each interview is presented with associated sound recordings, documents, and images. To avoid confusion in cases where multiple duplicative digital files were received for a given piece of content, such as a sound recording which has been saved in multiple file types, or an image for which there are several duplicates, only one file is listed in the finding aid.
Interviews are identified based on the ID number assigned by the Quilt Alliance. Generally, these IDs are formed by assigning the state abbreviation and zip code of the quilter’s home, followed by a number indicating the order in which the interview occurred. For example, "CA94121-002" would be the 2nd interview performed in the California zip code of 94121. In some cases, instead of a location-based ID, an acronym is used to indicate the project that the interview was a part of. For example, "BOQ-003" is the 3rd interview in the “Barack Obama Quilt” project. Just as often, there may be some combination of acronym and zip code, as is the case with all Daughters of the American Revolution (DAR) interviews.
For alphabetical list of Interviewees with associated interview numbers, see Appendix A.
For alphabetical list of Interviewers, see Appendix B.
Additional Guides
Completed finding aid is online. Preliminary finding aid (2007) with container list and concordance by format is available in the Folklife Reading Room, Library of Congress.
Acquisition
Quilt Alliance; 2007 to 2016.
Custodial History
From 1999 until January 2007, Quilt Alliance partnered with the University of Delaware, Center for Material Culture Studies, under the guidance of Dr. Bernard Herman, to house QSOS records. Since January 2007, the American Folklife Center has served as the repository for QSOS interview materials.
Accruals
Major accruals were received by the American Folklife Center from the Quilt Alliance in 2007, 2008, 2009, 2010 and 2013. The final accrual is expected in 2016.
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Access may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Electronic Format
Transcribed interviews and accompanying photographs are posted to the Quilt Alliance website which can be accessed at http://quiltalliance.org/projects/qsos/
Administrative History
The Quilt Alliance (formerly The Alliance for American Quilts) was formed in 1993 Shelly Zegart and Eunice Ray of the Kentucky Quilt Project, and Karey Bresenhan and Nancy O'Bryant, corporate officers of Quilts, Inc. and founders of the non-profit Texas Quilt Search, who saw the need to centralize information about quilts and quiltmaking.
In the fall of 1999, the Quilters’ S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories (QSOS) project was introduced by the Quilt Alliance and the International Quilt Festival (IQF). The initial training and interviews took place at the International Quilt Festival in Houston, Texas, in October of 1999. Former Quilt Alliance board members, Bernard Herman, Marcie Cohen Ferris, Patricia Keller and Patricia Crews developed the QSOS project. Karen Musgrave joined the group at the initial training and served for many years as a dedicated volunteer and QSOS taskforce chair.
The initial project was such a tremendous success that it was continued, with many additional volunteers spearheading regional QSOS projects, conducting interviews at quilt shows, guild meetings, and private homes across the country and around the world. Of note, one of these organizations is the Daughters of the American Revolution (DAR), a non-profit, non-political volunteer women’s organization founded in 1890 in Washington, D.C. In 2004 the DAR created a special position on their American Heritage Committee for QSOS, and has official representation on the Task Force of the Quilt Alliance.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of sound recordings, transcripts and photographic images documenting interviews conducted as a part of Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories (QSOS) project. QSOS is one of several projects and partnerships created by the Quilt Alliance in an effort to preserve, document, and share the lives and stories of quilters and quiltmaking. The project began in 1999 and continued though 2016.
QSOS is a grassroots project that utilizes volunteers from across the country to conduct and transcribe oral histories. Interviews are approximately 45 minutes in length and are usually conducted in person, but occasionally are conducted by phone or via e-mail.
Interviewees are encouraged to bring a "touchstone" quilt or other object to serve as a focus point for the interview. Rather than record comprehensive life histories, focused interviews target the conversation, for example, on quilt design, sources, techniques, inspiration, standards, and processes, along with other quilt-related topics.
The quilts represented in the collection vary widely in technique, style, and execution. Some are self-designed, while some follow traditional patterns or patterns by current designers. There are also historical quilts that date back to the mid-nineteenth to early twenty-first century. Among the quilt types seen in the collection are: hand quilts, machine-quilts (including long arm), traditional pattern quilts, scrap quilts, art quilts, round robin quilts, patriotic quilts and wearable art.
The QSOS project documents the complexity and diversity of quiltmakers and their quilts, creating a broadly accessible body of information concerning quiltmaking, both present-day and in living memory.
As of November 2016 the collection includes 1189 interviews, with all fifty US states, the United States Virgin Islands, and nine other countries represented including: Australia, Canada, Denmark, Georgia (Republic), Germany, Japan, Kenya, Peru, and Russia. The interviews are documented by sound recordings, transcripts and images, in a mix of physical and digital formats.
Earlier sound recordings of the interviews are largely on cassette tapes, with later interviews recorded on digital media in .wav, .wma, .mp3, .aif, and .cda formats. The images include both physical photographic prints and digital images in .jpg and .tif formats.
The majority of interviews have an associated draft and/or final versions of the transcript. The manuscripts associated with the interviews may also consist of a participant and quilt information form, correspondence, and promotional materials. These documents may be in a physical print format or in digital media in .doc, .docx, .pdf, or .rtf formats.
Digital media was received on a variety of carrier formats including compact disks, 3.5 in. floppy disks and zip disks.
Contents List
- Series 1: Administrative Files
  - Finding Aid, 2007-12, 126 pages (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Instrument of Gift, 2006-01-23, 4 pages (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Packing Lists and Miscellaneous Documentation. Processing Documentation. (Box-folder 1/3)
  - QSOS Background, 4 pages (Box-folder 1/4)
  - About QSOS, 2 pages (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Starting Your Own QSOS, 4 pages (Box-folder 1/6)
  - QSOS Manual, 58 pages (Box-folder 1/7)
  - QSOS Project Descriptions, 9 pages (Box-folder 1/8)
- Series 2: Interviews
  - Los hilos de la vida QSOS
    Karen Musgrave, QSOS volunteer, conducted interviews with the quiltmakers and their teachers in the mostly Latina quilt group, Los hilos de la vida, in Boonville, California. The interviews were made possible by a grant from the Salser Family Foundation.
    - Molly Johnson Martinez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-05 (Interview-id CA95415-01)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_01_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_01_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_01_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR493
    - Yolanda Ibarra oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-05 (Interview-id CA95415-02)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_02_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_02_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_02_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR494
    - Olga Medina oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-05 (Interview-id CA95415-03)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_03_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_03_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_03_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR495
    - Angeles Segura oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-05 (Interview-id CA95415-04)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_04_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_04_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_04_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR496
    - Lee Serrie oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-05 (Interview-id CA95415-05)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_05_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_05_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_05_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR497
    - Marlen Gaxiola oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-05 (Interview-id CA95415-06)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_06_04.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_06_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_06_02.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_06_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR498
    - Maria Padilla oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-07)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_07_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_07_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_07_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR499
    - Evangelina Angulo oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-08)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_CA95415_08_01.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_08_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR500
    - Jennifer McCoy oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-09)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_09_02.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_09_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_09_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR501
    - Maria Ramirez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-10)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_10_04.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_10_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_10_02.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_10_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR502
    - Luz Maria Carillo oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-11)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_11_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_11_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_11_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR503
    - Juan Sanchez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-12)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_CA95415_12_01.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_12_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR504
    - Luis Sanchez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-13)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_13_02.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_13_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_13_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR505
    - Paola Sanchez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-14)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_14_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_14_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_14_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR506
    - Emily Martinez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-06 (Interview-id CA95415-15)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_15_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_15_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_15_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR507
    - Tina Perez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-16)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_16_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_16_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_16_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR508
    - Juan Pablo oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-17)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_17_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_17_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_17_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR509
    - Angela Grijalba oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-18)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_18_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_18_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_18_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR510
    - Alma Mendoza oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-19)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_19_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_19_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_19_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR511
    - Carmela Madrigal oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-20)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_20_04.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_20_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_20_02.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_20_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR512
    - Teresa Malfavon oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-21)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_21_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_21_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_21_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR513
    - Mayte Guerro oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-22)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_22_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_22_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_22_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR514
    - Teresa Alvarez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-23)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_23_02.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_23_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_23_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR515
    - Lourdes Barragan oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-07 (Interview-id CA95415-24)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_24_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_24_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_24_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR516
    - Deanna Apfel oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-08 (Interview-id CA95415-25)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_25_02.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_25_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_25_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR517
    - Bertha Arizmendi oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-08 (Interview-id CA95415-26)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_26_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_26_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_26_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR518
    - Carl Johnson oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-08 (Interview-id CA95415-27)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_27_03.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_27_01.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_27_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR519
    - Mirella Mendoza oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-08 (Interview-id CA95415-28)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_28_01.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_28_02.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_28_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR520
    - Elvia Hernandez oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-08 (Interview-id CA95415-29)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_CA95415_29_02.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_29_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR521
    - Blanca Garcia oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-08 (Interview-id CA95415-30)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_CA95415_30_01.doc; afc2007009_CA95415_30_02.jpg; afc2007009_CA95415_30_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR522
    - Karina Mejia oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2007-03-08 (Interview-id CA95415-31)